https://www.academycollege.edu/privacy-policy/

First Name*Last Name*Email*
Phone*AddressCityStateZipHow did you find us?How did you find us?Search EngineFacebook/InstagramReferralWorld of Aviation/The PatriotWCCOThunderbird ReferralOtherArea of interest?Area of interest?AviationBusinessAccountingComputer TechnologyMessageCAPTCHAPhoneThis field is for validation purposes and should be left unchanged.
Privacy Policy
Academy College respects the privacy of its visitors. If you have any questions about the operation of our website, please email webmaster@academycollege.edu.
Our website collects names, email addresses, and other personal information from visitors only when submitted via one of our online forms, such as our pay online form and inquiry form. This data is used solely by Academy College and is not shared, traded, or sold to third parties.
Our website also collects non-personal data through the use of server-based “session variables,” which we use to achieve important site functionality, including the recognition of logged-in users and the secure passing of shopping cart information. In order to identify customers as they proceed through the check out process, our website also may use “cookies” (a small file stored by your browser on your hard drive used to carry data about your session from one page of the website to another or to identify you to the site between visits); thus, online transactions require a browser that accepts “cookies.” Some pages may not function properly if cookies are disabled in your web browser. If after submitting your information to our website you decide at some later date that you no longer wish to receive e-mail based advertising simply follow the “Opt Out” contained within the body of the email message you received.
Our web-server also records IP addresses from all visitors to our site. An IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer when you use the Internet. We use IP addresses to help diagnose problems with our server, to administer our site, to analyze trends, to track user movement, and to gather broad demographic information — all for the purpose of continually improving our website and delivering content. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information, and their collection is standard procedure in most web-server environments. Our website may utilize third party service providers to provide special services such as payment processors and Live Chat systems.  These third parties are prohibited from using your personally identifiable information for promotional purposes.
Our website contains links to other websites. Please note that when you click on one of these links, you are entering another website, for which Academy College is not responsible.  Academy College does not endorse such sites and is not responsible for the collection or use of your personal information on any external sites.  Links are provided as potential sources of information only.
This policy may be revised periodically without notice. Please re-read this policy prior to submitting any personal information if you have concerns about how your information is being collected and used.
An invitation to explore!
Contact Form
First Name*Last Name*Phone Number*Email*
AddressCityStateZip CodeHow did you hear about us?Search EngineFacebook/InstagramReferralWorld of Aviation/The PatriotWCCOThunderbird Aviation ReferralEmailOtherMessageArea of interest?
Flight
Aircraft Dispatch
Business
Accounting
Information Technology
Aviation Business
CAPTCHA
